Michael Urbanek

Staff Pharmacist - Philidor Rx Services, LLC

Bensalem, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Michael-Urbanek/7213a1434b13c023

Experienced Pharmacist with 5 years of professional healthcare experience. Dependable, loyal professional committed to provide extraordinary patient care and satisfaction. Enthusiastic, goal-oriented individual focused on encouraging team efforts to obtain a productive work environment.

- Proficient in Clinical Databases (Clinical Pharmacology, Lexicomp, UptoDate, Pubmed)
- Anticoagulant Therapy Monitoring and Counseling
- Drug Information
- Pharmaceutical Compounding
- Evidence-based Practice

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Staff Pharmacist

Philidor Rx Services, LLC - Hatboro, PA - 2015 to Present

- Verified and dispensed prescriptions for specialty pharmacy targeted to dispense 2.5M prescriptions in 2015
- Consulted patients and physicians on drug therapy and possible adverse reactions
- Educated and counseled patients in proper use of specialty medications
- Provided final checks prior to medications being shipped to patients
- Monitored and supervised up to 20 Pharmacy Technicians in daily workflow

Staff Pharmacist

CVS Pharmacy - 2011 to Present

Processed, verified, and dispensed prescriptions to customers in various community settings

- Consistently increased prescription sales by an average of 12% over 6 stores
- Improved customer satisfaction with store service level by an average of 14% over 6 stores

Pharmacy Intern

CVS Pharmacy - 2007 to 2011

Reviewed, processed, and dispensed prescriptions to a large diverse patient population under a supervising licensed Pharmacist

Awarded Certificate of Excellence for outstanding performance by a Pharmacy Grad Intern

Senior Clinical Intensive Case Manager

Penndel Mental Health Center - Penndel, PA - 1999 to 2007

- Mentored / trained new incoming case management staff in daily workflow and procedures and intervened when necessary in escalated situations
- · Reviewed staff documentation of service plans for quality review

Clinical Intensive Case Manager

Penndel Mental Health Center - 1998 to 1999

· Coordinated outpatient psychiatric treatment for caseload of 40 adolescents and adults

- Assisted patients in accessing local community resources in community
- Provided 24-hour crisis intervention / emergency management services to all patients of mental health foundation
- Completed and filed outcome reports for the Bucks County Office of Mental Health

(215) 6224968 Michael.urbanek215@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Doctor of Pharmacy in Pharmacy

Temple University

Bachelor of Science in Psychology

DeSales University

Bachelor of Arts in Criminal Justice

DeSales University